

PERSONAL DETAILS

DATE OF BIRTH:

25/07/1996

ID:

9607255063086

PASSPORT:

A05109023

ADDRESS:

91 Kingsley Road Bluff

LANGUAGES:

English & Afrikaans

DRIVERS LICENSE:

Code 8

CONTACT

PHONE:

+27 606966232

EMAIL:

divan.debruin25@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Computer Literate MS Word, Excel, Outlook & PowerPoint
- Excellent communication skills
- Friendly, courteous & service oriented
- Leadership & teamwork
- Strong work ethic

HOBBIES

- Gyming
- Travelling
- Hiking
- Reading

DIVAN DE BRUIN

Hard-working and driven Public Relations Officer with the ability to cultivate strong business relationships and lead productivity. Known for demonstrating superior interpersonal skills and influencing clear and effectual client relationships. Eager and ready to bring my knowledge, expertise, and passion to a new company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Public Relations Officer AMS Attorneys Inc 2019–Present

Brand Ambassador Rogue Models 2015–2019

Waiter & Bartender Lords & Legends 2014-2016

EDUCATION

TEFL Fullcircle

Advanced 120 Hours Certificate in Teaching English as a Foreign Language (TEFL) 2021

SimTech Training & Development Institution

Basic Plumbing Course 2019

IIE Varsity College Durban North

Honors in Management & Leadership 2018

IIE Varsity College Durban North

Bachelor of Commerce – Marketing Management 2017

REFERENCES

Cherise Jewnarain – AMS Attorneys Inc

+27 817153444 | 12jewnch@gmail.com

Tanya Cheyne - Rogue Models

+27 823124188

Deon Lottering - Lords & Legends

+27 815568280 | lottering7@hotmail.com